My name is Pinkie Pie
我名叫碧琪派
Hello!
你好!
And I am here to say
我喜欢开派对
How ya doin'?
怎么样？
I'm gonna make you smile
传播快乐与精彩
And I will brighten up your day
让生活充满滋味
It doesn't matter now
不管什么烦恼
What's up?
你好吗？
If you are sad or blue
不必悲伤痛苦
Howdy!
你好！
'Cuz cheering up my friends
有我碧琪在这，负面情绪都会消除
is just what Pinkie's here to do
'Cuz I love to make you smile, smile, smile
我只想让你们开心愉快
Yes I do!
和幸福
It fills my heart with sunshine all the while
温暖阳光让我心潮澎湃
Yes it does!
像这样
'Cuz all I really need's a smile, smile, smile
只要让大家都笑口常开
我的心跟着豪迈
From these happy friends of mine
I like to see you grin!
我想看你高兴
Awesome!
很好！
I love to see you beam!
我想让你开心
Rock on!
一起!
The corners of your mouth turned up
你愉快的笑容就是我的毕生追寻
is always Pinkie's dream
Hoof bump!
击掌!
But if you're kind of worried
即使你垂头丧气
And your face is made of frown
或是被琐事困扰
I'll work your heart and do my best
我都会尽平生最大努力让你开怀大笑
To turn that sad frown upside down
'Cuz I love to make you grin, grin, grin
我只想让你们玩得尽兴
Yes I do!
和幸福
Busted out from ear to ear, let it begin
让笑声口耳相传永不停
Just give me a joyful grin, grin, grin
你们的快乐让我欢欣
And you fill me with good cheer
这是最好的赠礼
It's true, some days are dark and lonely
有时生活会充满难题
And maybe you feel sad
可能无法消解
But Pinkie will be there to show you that it isn't that bad
但碧琪会努力帮你翻过悲伤的那一页
There is one thing that makes me happy
只有一件事能让我觉得万分精彩
And makes my whole life worthwhile
And that's when I talk to my friends and get them to smile
那就是我和朋友们一起乐开怀
I really am so happy
我真的兴奋不已
Your smile fills me with glee
笑容令我惊喜
I give a smile, I get a smile
你们大笑让我也笑
And that's so special to me!
这一切都有意义
'Cuz I love to see you beam, beam, beam
我只想让你们欢笑不停
Yes I do!
和幸福
Tell me what more can I say
告诉我如何才能
to make you see
让你明晰
That I do!
和清楚
It makes me happy when you beam, beam, beam
你们的笑容能让我欣喜
Yes, it always makes my day
这让我活力充沛
Come on everypony, smile, smile, smile
来吧各位小马来，来，来
Fill my heart up with sunshine, sunshine
让心灵绽放光彩，光彩
All I really need's a smile, smile, smile
我们大家一起乐开怀
From these happy friends of mine
让我们活出精彩
Come on everypony, smile, smile, smile
来吧各位小马来，来，来
Fill my heart up with sunshine, sunshine
让心灵绽放光彩，光彩
All I really need's a smile, smile, smile
我们大家一起乐开怀
From these happy friends of mine
让我们活出精彩
Yes the perfect gift for me
唯一完美的赠礼
Come on everypony, smile, smile, smile!
来吧各位小马来，来，来
Fill my heart up with sunshine, sunshine!
让心灵绽放光彩，光彩
Is a smile as wide as a mile
是大家微笑一排排
All I really need's a smile, smile, smile!
我们大家一起乐开怀
To make me happy as can be
这又是何等的美丽
From these happy friends of...
我们的生活充满...
Smile Smile Smile Smile
精彩 精彩 精彩 精彩
Smile
精彩
Come on and
充满
Smile
精彩
Come on and smile
绽放光彩